// Questions - Reputation

export const reputationQuestions = [
    {
    "question": "And he can be my jailer, Burton to this Taylor ",
    "answers": ["Dont' Blame Me", "...Ready for It?", "Dress", "Delicate"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "So here's the truth from my red lips",
    "answers": ["End Game", "I Did Something Bad", "King of My Heart", "Getaway Car"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "But if he drops my name, then I owe him nothin'",
    "answers": ["Gorgeous", "New Years Day", "Delicate", "I Did Something Bad"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I've been breakin' hearts a long time",
    "answers": ["Dress", "Getaway Car", "Don't Blame Me", "End Game"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Is it chill that you're in my head?",
    "answers": ["Delicate", "Gorgeous", "Dress", "...Ready for It?"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Honey, I rose up from the dead, I do it all the time",
    "answers": ["Dress", "Look What You Made Me Do", "So it Goes", "Gorgeous"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "See you in the dark, all eyes on you, my magician",
    "answers": ["Getaway Car", "New Years Day", "Delicate", "So it Goes"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "But if you're single that's honestly worse",
    "answers": ["Gorgeous", "Don't Blame Me", "End Game", "...Ready for It?"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "It hit you like a shotgun shot to the heart",
    "answers": ["King of My Heart", "So it Goes", "Getaway Car", "Don't Blame Me"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "And all at once, you are the one I have been waiting for",
    "answers": ["Gorgeous", "Delicate", "Dress", "King of My Heart"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Say my name and everything just stops",
    "answers": ["Dress", "So It Goes", "King of My Heart", "End Game"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "But I stay when it's hard or it's wrong or we're makinâ€™ mistakes",
    "answers": ["Delicate", "I Did Something Bad", "...Ready for It?", "New Year's Day"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Knew he was a killer first time that I saw him",
    "answers": ["Getaway Car", "...Ready for It?", "So it Goes", "Don't Blame Me"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I swear I don't love the drama, it loves me",
    "answers": ["Gorgeous", "King of My Heart", "End Game", "New Year's Day"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I never trust a narcissist, but they love me",
    "answers": ["I Did Something Bad", "Look What You Made Me Do", "End Game", "Gorgeous"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Dive bar on the East Side, where you at?",
    "answers": ["So it Goes", "Delicate", "...Ready for It?", "Dress"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I don't like your little games",
    "answers": ["Dress", "End Game", "New Year's Day", "Look What You Made Me Do"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "You did a number on me but, honestly, baby, who's countin'?",
    "answers": ["King of My Heart", "So it Goes", "Getaway Car", "End Game"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "You should think about the consequence of your magnetic field being a little too strong",
    "answers": ["Gorgeous", "Delicate", "Don't Blame Me", "Dress"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Think about the place where you first met me",
    "answers": ["End Game", "Getaway Car", "Look What You Made Me Do", "...Ready for It?"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Salute to me, I'm your American Queen ",
    "answers": ["Delicate", "So it Goes", "Gorgeous", "King of My Heart"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "'Cause I don't want you like a best friend",
    "answers": ["Dress", "End Game", "I Did Something Bad", "New Year's Day"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "There's glitter on the floor after the party",
    "answers": ["Delicate", "New Year's Day", "...Ready for It?", "Gorgeous"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "And I bury hatchets but I keep maps of where I put 'em",
    "answers": ["New Year's Day", "So it Goes", "End Game", "Delicate"],
    "correct": 2
    },
    
    {
    "question": "For you, I would cross the line, I would waste my time",
    "answers": ["Don't Blame Me", "...Ready for It?", "Gorgeous", "Getaway Car"],
    "correct": 0
    },

]